<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>A collection of thoughts, photos, and places.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodope Mountains</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-06-rhodope.jpeg&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Photo of grey sky, snow covered road and trees, and a car with one headlight driving toward the photographer. A snow covered car is parked on the right.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, I can’t quite tell the difference between hot and cold, but most of the time I can’t tell the difference between any two opposites anyway. These days it seems like my alternate reality is getting blurred with what people call the real world as asleep gets more confused with awake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have been talking to me like this isn’t your first time with those pestering whys and hows and whos and whats. (Have you ever asked a crazy person to explain what makes them crazy)—I wouldn’t recommend it. (You might get caught in the parentheses, too.) Well, it isn’t exactly my first time either…caught inside the parenthesis) and overusing the ellipsis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 11:17:01 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/rhodope-mountains/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/rhodope-mountains/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three Sisters</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-05-three-sisters.JPG&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Photo of the Three Sisters rock formation in Katoomba, Australia.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder if we would have traveled together. I wonder if years after we lived together, after we grew apart but still called each other best friend, we would have met up in a foreign, farfetched city. I wonder if you would have stayed at a hostel or if you would have preferred a hotel (you always preferred hotels). I wonder if we would have had another sunrise night like when we were 19, or if you would have insisted on something more mature, dinner and drinks, an early night. I wonder if you would have visited me now, thousands of miles away, made a vacation out of it, let me be your tour guide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 20:40:01 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/three-sisters/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/three-sisters/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jerusalem</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-04-jerusalem.jpg&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Photo of a lit up Shabat Operation elevator button.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I retreat, sometimes, into the depths of my mind. When I’m with people, it can happen without me noticing. One moment I’m present, and the next, I’m gone. Aren’t you having any fun, someone asks. Why? To me, I only withdrew for a moment, but it was noticed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to rest, sometimes, when I’m supposed to be having fun being alive. There have been times when I couldn’t, wouldn’t, refused, to match everyone else’s energy. I need to rest, I say. To which I hear back: but it’s once-in-a-lifetime. It wasn’t, for me, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 20:55:18 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/jerusalem/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/jerusalem/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-03-rugby.jpeg&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Close up of printing press letters spelling Historic Rugby Commissary.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m quitting my job to become a writer, to work on that famous war novel I’m always telling everyone about. I’m moving to South Africa to find my muse. I will only wear white linen dresses. I will bury myself in my basement and take too many sleeping pills (but not too much). I will go on a two-week bender and write my most famous work on one scroll of paper. No editing is required. Straight to the publisher, please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 21:33:23 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/rugby/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/rugby/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oslo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-02-oslo.JPG&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Low angle photo of wood paneling inside Oslo Opera House.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quiet, like the snow. In the first few moments, blissful. In the next, exciting. As it sinks in, knowing it will have to melt (unless), but yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 17:58:16 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/oslo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/oslo/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lexington</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-10-01-lexington.jpg&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Low angle photo of dozens of carved pumpkins on stone steps.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The desert air outside is dusty, humid, still stifling almost every day, but something inside: inside, it feels like autumn. Cool air lingers, the AC must be set just right. Inside, it feels like sweaters and sleeping with the windows open, a cool breeze to lull me to sleep each night and gently wake me up the next day. Something inside feels like the Southeast on an early October night. Maybe its my memory playing tricks on me, knowing I’m homesick—for a time, not a place.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 04:25:16 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/lexington/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/lexington/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Al-Khazneh</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-09-30-al-khazneh.JPG&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Five camels with saddles and bridles in front of the red carved sandstone rocks in Petra, Jordan.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;55 to the Red Line. Transfer to Blue. Trying to save a few dollars by taking public transit, losing time instead of money. I rationalize, this is the penny-pinching that will help me dig myself out from under my debts (is this picking myself up by my boot straps?). Careful preparation: will I make all my transfers? Will I make it in time before the start of the play?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the play, drinks. After the drinks, a decision. My frugality and financial anxiety takes over again, refusing an offer to spend more time with a friend to take advantage of a ride-share coupon—it expires at midnight!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Months, or maybe it is years, later my mind is returning to this memory, wondering why there never was we, realizing I didn’t turn down a midnight drink but a proposition, a potentiality. All for the sake of saving five dollars.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 17:16:48 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/al-khazneh/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/al-khazneh/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Serowe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-09-29-serowe.JPG&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Top two thirds is gradient sky from dark purple into pinks and then orange. Top left is a crescent moon. Bottom third is black outlines of savannah flora.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sleeping well these days. Something keeps me up at night. I can’t quiet my mind when there’s still so many thoughts to think like, what’s stopping me from sleep? Something keeps me up at night. I don’t know what, but it doesn’t wake me up in the morning either. Something keeps me up at night. I’m passing the time &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/playlist/7KgNENnu7NgSon3y7lZuqF?si=OaZs3rYKRnmUeyVZXgOpKQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dancing to the beat of my own mental break&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 08:52:45 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/serowe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/serowe/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Stone Wedding</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-09-28-stone-wedding.jpg&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Photo from behind and below of the rock formation Stone Wedding. Small plants and shrubs on ground and some parts of rocks. Sky in upper quarter is light gray.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because being missed is a much greater feeling than being loved I kept my distance and never told you how I felt. Now, I’m gone and so are you, but you miss me like I love you. Blaming the rain on missed turns won’t cover up the fact that these old roads aren’t familiar anymore. Maybe this distance is what we’ve needed: A separation of miles, not minds. I swear you loved me once—your songs still play inside my head. Because I still think you might love me one day, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/playlist/6ul1IOR2ltUyj9D8Ncc9hy?si=2dYW1vTFQSSiPfAOTRAuwQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;these are the songs I would play&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 10:00:05 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/stone-wedding/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/stone-wedding/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Piazzale Michelangelo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//images.weserv.nl/?url=havemapswill.travel/img/2020-09-27-perseus.png&amp;amp;&amp;amp;w=500h=400&amp;amp;dpr=3&quot; alt=&quot;Photo of the Perseus With Medusa's Head bronze sculpture on top of white marble platform. Perseus stands upon Medusa's body and holds her head up. Background of photo shows outdoor pavilion overhead.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A time lapse plays across my mind as I am making my way up to Piazzale Michelangelo. Moving through the Renaissance streets I’m quiet but projecting, trying to imagine my life as a Botticelli dreamscape. Pausing in front of Dante’s childhood home, I dream of the places I have been, where I was, why I needed to run. Oh, Perseus, why?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 11:16:27 +0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//blog/piazzale-michelangelo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//blog/piazzale-michelangelo/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
